{
    "id": "57a9991cc6764b589c1325878c7215ab",
    "title": "Spelling And Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The army’s disorganized retreat was ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ignominous",
                "ignominious",
                "ignominius"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e0cc098edbb34238b79f9d18bdf40c75"
        },
        {
            "question": "Individualists cannot accept community ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "idology",
                "ideology",
                "ideologi"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36a999c55c7c4fb89832576fc4cb7aa9"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. of the law is no excuse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Ignorance",
                "Ignoranse",
                "Ignorrance"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39718a50645d42ecbd91ccb53a3acfd9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Spring makes everyone feel ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "idol",
                "idle",
                "idlle"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "271ebeef576c41099ac4dbb5a4ebeaab"
        },
        {
            "question": "The senator showed his ………………………………. by saying he was for the bill and then voting against it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hypocrisy",
                "hipocricy",
                "hyppocricy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e3944afa88945168fa65ff6864a33b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The medical students were asked how they would treat a ………………………….. illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hipothetical",
                "hypothetical",
                "hypotheticcal"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f22ae9af42c4c6fa40f1f2f4b4d504d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Both parents grew ……………………………… when they couldn’t find the child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hysterical",
                "histerical",
                "hysterycal"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da23aca2576b435abae04865c18deeff"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is the ……………………………. among us who try to aid humanity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "idolists",
                "idealists",
                "ideolists"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e329886cccd243cd88f85bcf1f51fa1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor gave an …………………………. of the dangers of poor nutrition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "illustration",
                "ilustration",
                "illustrasion"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "93eba6214433428c83e52479108afb82"
        },
        {
            "question": "The artist’s …………………………… use of color delighted the critics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "imaginative",
                "imaginetive",
                "immaginative"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c28f36b4de74f23ae2599ce75731d1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was an …………………………. actor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ilustrious",
                "illustrious",
                "illustrous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dca47365eb414a36b35c8a7f3da7b5ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fabric isn’t real silk, only an ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "immitation",
                "imtation",
                "imitation"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "25ed47acc3d44eca8b9adea74c080669"
        }
    ]
}